Arielle Tsabar

Experienced DevOps engineer, Skilled in Linux OS, Cloud-provisioning, CI-CD, Kubernetes. A fast learner, enthusiastic about new technologies, A team player with great interpersonal skills, hard working and creative thinker, with a can-do attitude. Tel Aviv

0548363142

arielzabar@gmail.com LinkedIn arielle-tsabar

EXPERIENCE

Totango - DevOps

March 2022 - present

- Managing multitude microservices in kubernetes using kops over spot instances in production environments, using GitOps methodology with jenkins as the CI, and an in house tool as the CD.
- Provisioning and maintaining AWS cloud resources using Terragrunt & Terraform while taking cost into consideration.
- Working with Elasticsearch clusters, MySQL databases, Kafka.
- Monitoring and alerting with Prometheus, Grafana, New Relic, AWS CloudWatch.

Ubimo, Quotinent - DevOps

March 2021 - March 2022

a part of a 2 member team that manages Ubimo's and Quotient subsidiaries infrastructure in GCP using Pulumi.

Deploying and managing services in Kubernetes (GKE) using Helm Charts, while using FluxCD to automate the CD process of kubernetes deployment.

Monitoring using Prometheus and Grafana stack, on top of K8s orchestrator. Including

Monitoring using Prometheus and Grafana stack, on top of K8s orchestrator, Including integration with On-Call platforms based on Prometheus Alertmanager. Implemented CI using TeamCity.

• MyHeritage - DevOps

January 2020 - March 2021

Built and maintained large scale infrastructure in terraform, using various providers - AWS, Vault, Consul.

Creating & managing Jenkins masters & workers in AWS cloud.

Developing build & deployment jobs using Groovy.

Experience with Amazon Web Sorvings, migration of an on provider.

Experience with Amazon Web Services, migration of an on-prem environment to the cloud, and maintaining the environment.

IDF Matzpen - QA

September 2018 - March 2019

QA tests of applications on systems in different Domains.

Oversighted the testing process, Identified test scenarios, estimated test effort and created test plans.

Prepared detailed reports on bugs and errors discovered after conducting post implementation testing.

IDF Mamram – System Administrator

March 2017 - September 2018

Monitoring and operation of Linux and Windows Server based applications, both physical and virtual.

Diagnosed and troubleshooted events in real time in a quick and effective manner in order to maintain availability SLA in our organization.

Building and deploying large scale systems using Docker,

Increasing team's efficiency by automating manual work using Python and bash. Administrating and Supporting MySQL and OracleDB Databases.

EDUCATION

DevOps Experts - "Advanced devops" course

SKILLS

Operating Systems:

Red Hat Enterprise Linux, Windows Server

Automation Languages:

Python, groovy, Kotlin DSL, Bash

Automation Tools:

Terraform, Jenkins, FluxCD, Docker, Kubernetes

Monitoring & Alerting Tools:

Grafana, Prometheus, New Relic

Version Control Tools: Git

Cloud Environments:

GCP, AWS, Amazon EC2, Lambda, RDS, S3, KMS, Kinesis

Databases: MySQL, AWS RDS

Basic Knowledge:

Kafka, Puppet, Ansible, chef

LANGUAGES

Hebrew - Native language **English** - Full professional proficiency

July 2020 - October 2020

IDF, Basmach - NTMM Course January 2017 - April 2017

Harel high school, Mevasseret zion September 2013 - June 2016

Majored in Biology, Computer Science and Computer Graphics.